Guide to the Occupy Wall Street Archives Working Group Records TAM.630
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Poster collected on November 14 -- Inequality makes my patients sick! PNHP Physicians for a National Health Program New York Metro Chapter, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with black marker, and white paper with green and black ink taped onto poster. Verso reads: "American exceptionalism." Except for: the poor, minorities, students, workers, immigrants, Native-Americans, et al and you!
- Poster collected on November 14 -- I'm a doctor for the 99% PNHP Physicians for a National Health Program New York Metro Chapter, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with black marker, and white paper with green and black ink taped onto poster. Verso reads: Thomas Jefferson said: "When I reflect that God is just, I tremble for my country." America: You will not be absolved of your crimes -against- humanity.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- #OccupierAdvocacy, address greivances, answer questions, navigate bureaucracy. How can we help?, 2011
  23" x 35" Peach poster paper with black marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- I'm the 99% fighting for my rights, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  22" x 28" White poster paper with black and red marker.
- Poster collected on November 14 -- We want butter not guns! Listen to us*, 2011 (Box 26)
  12.25" x 24" Brown cardboard with blue marker. Verso reads: Obama lied: No change, transparency, offshore accounts, savings, social security, run away inflation, endless wars
- Poster collected on November 14 -- I want to burn the Turkish flag. Belongs to 1% ruling class, 2011 (Box 8)
  23" x 24" Brown cardboard with black marker.
- Posters, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 5-6, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Folder 1-6, Box 18, Folder 4-5, Box 19, Folder 3-13, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Folder 1-8, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Folder 1-10, Box 35, Box 36, Folder 8-9, Box 37, Box 39, Flat-file-folder 4)
- Donation box, 2011 (Box 38)